Simon Flexner Papers 1891-1946 Mss.B.F365
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Simon Flexner Papers, 1891-1946; 115.5 linear feet
  - Russell, Frederick F., 1910-1938; 30 folders
    Includes: Correspondence on teaching bacteriology to members of the armed services at RIMR, including letters on fellows of RIMR who were members of Medical Reserve Corps. Correspondence on standardization of meningitis serum and its supply to army base hospitals. Correspondence on supply of laboratory "cars" to be used in emergencies in military camps to control communicable diseases. Report of SF to Russell on former's visit to Camps Jackson and Beauregard, February 1918. Correspondence on outbreaks of B. welchi and encephalitis in military camps, 1918. Preliminary reports by C. N. Leach on use of carbon tetrachloride in the treatment of hookworm disease, Manila, 1922. Administrative correspondence on work of International Health Board.
  - Russell, Helen
  - Russell, I. K.
  - Russell, J. Barbour
  - Russell, James E.
  - Russell, Lindsay
  - Russell, N. C.
  - Russell, Paul F.
  - Russell, W. W.
  - Russell, Walter
  - Russell, William L.
  - Russell Sage Foundation
  - Russell Sage Institute of Pathology
  - Russi, Mrs. J. A.
  - Russian Refugee Relief Society
  - Russian Telegraph Agency
  - Ruth, Edward S
  - Rutherford, G. J.
  - Rutledge, Benjamin Huger, Jr.
  - Ruvtz-Rees, Caroline
  - Ryan, Henry J.
  - Ryan, John D.
  - Ryerson, Edwin W.
  - Ryerson, Martin A.
  - Ryerson, Susan Parker
  - Rypins, Harold
  - Ryther, Henry Franklin
  - Sabin, Albert B.
  - Sabin, Florence Rena, 1913-1940; 5 folders
    - Sabin, Florence Rena, 4 folders
    - A Great Anatomist and Educator
  - Sabin, Mrs. L.
  - Sabin, Jane K.
  - Sachs, Bernard
  - Sachs, Erwin
  - Sachs, Hans
  - Sachs, Julius
  - Saddington, Charles
  - Saddington, Ronald Steele
  - Sa'di, Lutfi M.
  - Sadlier, James E.
  - Sachsisches Serumwerk
  - Saelhof, Clarence C.
  - Saengeri, Mrs. A. D.
  - Safford, M. Victor
  - Safran, Louis
  - Safran, Norman
  - Sage, Eben C.
  - Sager, Benson E.
  - Sahli, Hermann
  - Sailer, Joseph
  - Saint Bartholomew's Hospital
  - Saint Clair, F. W.
  - Saint Francis Hospital
  - Saint Gaudens, Hower
  - Saint George, A. V.
  - Saint George's School
  - Saint John, Fordyce Barker
  - Saint John, George C.
  - Saint John, H. W. and Co.
  - Saint John-Brooks, R.
  - Saint Joseph's Hospital
  - Saint Louis Medical Society
  - Saint Mary's Hospital
  - Saint Paul, Minn., State Dept. of Health
  - Sainte Marie, Phillippe
  - Saito, Hirosi
  - Salaman, Redcliffe N.
  - Salamonowicz, Arthur
  - Salanier, M.
  - Salant, Henry
  - Salant, William
  - Salas, Jose S.
  - Salfeld, H.
  - Salgues, R.
  - Salimbeni, Prof.
  - Salisbury, Donald W.
  - Salmon, David L.
  - Salmon, Robert
  - Salmon, Thomas W.
  - Salomon, Alfred V.
  - Salomon, Kurt
  - Salomon, Percy F.
  - Salomonsen, C.
  - Salter, P. P.
  - Saltonstall, John L.
  - Salvat y Navarro, Antonio
  - Salvemini, G.
  - Salvesen, Harold
  - Salzburg, Peter
  - Salzman, Jacob
  - Salzman, S. R.
  - Sambon, L. W.
  - Sammis, Ida B.
  - Sampson, A.
  - Samuels, J. A.
  - Samuels, W. J.
  - San Diego Naval Training Camp
  - San Marcos Hotel
  - San Ricart, R.
  - Sanarelli, G.
  - Sanborn, C. E.
  - Sanchez Gomez, Joaquin
  - Sand, Rene
  - Sandblad, A. G.
  - Sandefur, James F.
  - Sanders, C. K.
  - Sanders, J. G.
  - Sanderson, E. L.
  - Sanderson, Everett S.
  - Sanderson, Raymond
  - Sandler, Benjamin P.
  - Sandler, M.
  - Sandow, Alexander
  - Sands, Irving J.
  - Sands, William H.
  - Sandwith, F. M.
  - Sanes, K I.
  - Sanford, William W.
  - Sanger, Homer F.
  - Sanger, Margaret
  - Sansum, William D.
  - Santa Claus Association
  - Santesson, Lars
  - Santos, Joad V. De Los
  - Santow, Miss M.
  - Saperston, Sidney
  - Saphir, Joseph F.
  - Sargent, Edith
  - Sarton, George
  - Sasaki, Takaoki
  - Sastrel, Fernando
  - Sata, Aikiko
  - Sater, Clifford
  - Satterlee, G. Reese
  - Satterlee, Henry Suydam
  - Satterlee, Herbert L.
  - Satterlee, Mabel
  - Saturday Review
  - Saucedo O, Saturnino
  - Saumenig, F. B.
  - Saunders, A. P.
  - Saunders, E. W.
  - Saunders, Louise Brownell
  - Saunders, Silvia
  - Savage, Howard J.
  - Savage, Maud
  - Savage, W. G.
  - Savas, Const.
  - Saville, Thorndike
  - Sawada, Setsuzo
  - Sawiros, B.
  - Sawyer, Charles J.
  - Sawver, Philip
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A., 5 folders
  - Saylor, Howard L.
  - Sayre, Reginald H.
  - Scadron, Gene
  - Scales, Miss
  - Scammell, M. E.
  - Scammon, Clarence L.
  - Scandrett, Richard B., Jr.
  - Scanlon, T. F.
  - Scannell, James J.
  - Scarborough, H. V.
  - Scarlett, E. P.
  - Scatchard, George, 1926; 4 items
    Includes: Letters on his visit to RIMR, with special reference to developing physical chemistry at RIMR.
  - Schachner, August
  - Schackno, Henry G.
  - Schadt, George L.
  - Schaefer, John H.
  - Schaefer, Walter
  - Schaeffer, Asa A.
  - Schaeffer, Morris
  - Schafer, Edward A.
  - Schafer, Myron
  - Schaffner, Charles E.
  - Schaibel, F. P.
  - Schain, Josephine E.
  - Schamberg, Jay Frank
  - Schamberg, Morris I.
  - Schank, William
  - Schano, Juliana
  - Schapiro, Louis
  - Schebat, Leon
  - Scheel, Victor
  - Scheffer, I. Herbert
  - Schegal, Dr.
  - Scheiman, Berthold
  - Scheinman, Blanche
  - Schenach, Anton
  - Schenken, Dr.
  - Schepelmann, Dr.
  - Schereschewsky, J. W.
  - Scherff, W. A.
  - Scherp, Henry W.
  - Scherp, Dr.: Nasal Mucosa and Tonsil Experiments
  - Schieffelin, William Jay
  - Schick, Bela
  - Schiff, Jacob H.
  - Schiffer, Rudolph
  - Schiller, Walter
  - Schilling, Claus
  - Schirm, Mr.
  - Schlacht, Abraham S.
  - Schlaepfer, Charles
  - Schlaepfer, Karl
  - Schlapp, Max
  - Schleifstein, J.
  - Schleuder, H. W.
  - Schlomovitz, B. H.
  - Schloss, Oscar M.
  - Schlossman, Arthur
  - Schlutz, F. W.
  - Schmahl, P. J. R.
  - Schmeisser, Harry C.
  - Schmid, H. Ernest
  - Schmidlapp, William Horace
  - Schmidt, Friedrich W.
  - Schmidt, Hans
  - Schmidt, Louis
  - Schmidt, Louis E.
  - Schmidt, Mrs. Otto
  - Schmidt, Paul
  - Schmidt, Sara Sellers
  - Schmidt-Ott, F.
  - Schmiepen, Dr.
  - Schmitt, Aaron F.
  - Schnabel, Alfred
  - Schnabel, Truman G.
  - Schneider, Mrs. W. B.
  - Schneider, William F.
  - Schnein, Martin
  - Schneller, M. R.
  - Schnittkind, Henry T.
  - Schoen, Louis
  - Schoenwald, Gerhart
  - Scholink, Maxwell H.
  - Scholtz, J. H., Jr.
  - School Desk Top Corporation
  - Schorer, Edwin Henry
  - Schorling, Raleigh
  - Schrader, Alleyne von
  - Schram, Mildred W. S.
  - Schrama, Andrew
  - Schreiner, Edmund
  - Schreve, Joseph C.
  - Schroeder, C. R.
  - Schroeder, J. Henry
  - Schroeder, Mrs. William H.
  - Schrotter, Hermann von
  - Schryner, Hazel M.
  - Schubert, Maxwell P.
  - Schuchert, C.
  - Schunemann-Hofer, G. A.
  - Schuhmann, Rev. G.
  - Schuld, William, Jr.
  - Schulhof, Kamil
  - Schulman Brothers
  - Schultz, E. W.
  - Schultz, Hedwig
  - Schultz, Oscar T.
  - Schulze-Gocht, Dr.
  - Schumann, Carl
  - Schurer, F.
  - Schurman, J. G.
  - Schurter, P. J.
  - Schuster, Sir Arthur
  - Schuster, Julius
  - Schuster, Norah H.
  - Schuyler, Margaretta Van Rensslaer
  - Schuyler, William M.
  - Schwab, Dr.
  - Schwab, Bessie Flexner
  - Schwalbe, Dr.
  - Schwartz, Mrs.
  - Schwartz, Charles Wadsworth
  - Schwartz, J.
  - Schwartz, J. R.
  - Schwartz, Samuel
  - Schwartz, Saul A.
  - Schwartze, E. W.
  - Schwartzman, Gregory
  - Schwarz, Emil
  - Schwarz, J. C.
  - Schwebs, Mrs. M. von
  - Schweintz, G. E. de
  - Schwentker, Francis F.
  - Science Press
  - Science Service
  - Scientific American
  - Scipio, L. A.
  - Scofield, Walter E.
  - Scott, Mr.
  - Scott, A. B.
  - Scott, A. J.
  - Scott, Mrs. Albert B.
  - Scott, Albert L.
  - Scott, Gordon H.
  - Scott, Harry W.
  - Scott, Hugh L.
  - Scott, J. W.
  - Scott, J. W. Robertson
  - Scott, John W.
  - Scott, Mrs. Joseph Alison
  - Scott, Katherine J.
  - Scott, M. J.
  - Scott, W.
  - Scott, W. J. M.
  - Scott, W. W.
  - Scotts, Dorothy
  - Scremin, Ling
  - Scribner's Magazine
  - Scringer, Mrs. George
  - Scripture, E. W.
  - Scripture, May K.
  - Scruggs, W. M.
  - Scudder, Charles L.
  - Scudder, Mary Theresa
  - Scull, D. E.
  - Sculley, Clarence C.
  - Seabrook, M. V.
  - Seabrook, William
  - Seager, Henry R.
  - Seaman, Louis L.
  - Seares, F. H.
  - Searle, C. Howard
  - Sears, Frederick W.
  - Sears, Heber J.
  - Sears, Russell A.
  - Sears, Roebuck and Company
  - Seashore, C. E.
  - Sedgwick, Ellery
  - Sedgwick, W. T.
  - See, T. J. J.
  - Seeb, Hans
  - Seede, Harriett G.
  - Seeley, John
  - Seelig, M. G.
  - Seeligman, Gustav
  - Seem, Ralph B.
  - Seeman, W. H.
  - Seerichs, H. W.
  - Segali, M.
  - Seger, George N.
  - Seham, M.
  - Seibert, E. G.
  - Seidelin, Harald
  - Seidlin, S. M.
  - Seiffers National Booksellers
  - Seiffert, G.
  - Seifried, Oskar
  - Seiler, Charles E.
  - Seiler, J. H.
  - Seinfeld, S. G.
  - Seligman, Mrs. Isaac
  - Selignac, Henri
  - Selkin, William
  - Sellards, Andrew W.
  - Seller, D. S.
  - Discussion of Dr. Leach's Paper on Comparative Methods of Diagnosis of Rabies in Animals
  - Selsor, M. A.
  - Semken, George H.
  - Sempe, Jorge
  - Semple, Patty
  - Sen, Anil Kumar
  - Sendroy, Julius, Jr.
  - Senftner, Herman F.
  - Senior, Frank S., 2 folders
  - Senior, H. D.
  - Senior, James B.
  - Senn, Thomas J.
  - Serbian Child Welfare Association of America
  - Sergeant, Elizabeth
  - Serra, J. H.
  - Serrano, Tomas
  - Serrati, M.
  - Sette, O. E.
  - Sewall, Henry, 1913-1934; ca. 30 items
  - Seward, Sir Albert C.
  - Sexton, L. A.
  - Seyd, Felizia
  - Seymour, Gertrude
  - Seymour, Morris W.
  - Seymour, N. Gilbert
  - Shaare Zedek Hospital
  - Shackley, Ernest V.
  - Shadgen, Joseph F.
  - Shafer, Homer
  - Shaffer, Mary
  - Shaffer, Philip A., 1914-1936; ca. 20 items
  - Shakespeare Press
  - Shallenberger, Gertrude
  - Shallenberger, William F.
  - Shambaugh, G. E.
  - Shamoff, Vladimir M.
  - Shanghai Medical School
  - Shanks, David C.
  - Shanks, Edgar D.
  - Shaper, A. A.
  - Shapiro, A. A.
  - Shapiro, Ann
  - Shapiro, Celia
  - Shapiro, Isidor F.
  - Shapley, Harlow
  - Sharp, Charles E.
  - Sharp, E. A.
  - Sharpe, C. G.
  - Sharpe, Elizabeth
  - Sharpless, Frederick C.
  - Shattuck, Frederick C.
  - Shattuck, George Cheever
  - Shaughnessy, Charles S.
  - Shaughnessy, Howard J.
  - Shaw, Edward B.
  - Shaw, Ellen Eddy
  - Shaw, Frank S.
  - Shaw, H. H.
  - Shaw, Henry A.
  - Shaw, Henry K.
  - Shaw, Henry Larned Keith
  - Shaw, Myra M.
  - Shaw, Robert P.
  - Shea, John J.
  - Shea, William E.
  - Sheard, Charles
  - Shearer, Creswell
  - Shearer, J. O.
  - Shedd, George Harold
  - Sheehan, J. Eastman
  - Sheehan, Thomas J., Jr.
  - Shelby, Evan
  - Sheldon, A. M.
  - Sheldon, Caroline Munro
  - Sheldon, Edward W.
  - Sheldon, H. H.
  - Sheldon, Paul B.
  - Sheldrick, Roland
  - Shelley, Imelda
  - Shellman, Arthur P.
  - Shenehon, Eleanor
  - Shepard, James E.
  - Shepard, Morgan
  - Shepard, William Gamaliel
  - Shepardson, Dwight E.
  - Shepley, Henry E.
  - Sheppard, Jeanie Ramsey
  - Sheppard, Philip A. B.
  - Sheppard, R. L.
  - Sheppard, William T.
  - Sheppe, W. M.
  - Shera, J. Fletcher
  - Sherman, E. A.
  - Sherman, Ethel M.
  - Sherman, Franklin, Jr.
  - Sherman, G. H.
  - Sherman, J. M.
  - Sheman, Lillian
  - Sheman, M. S.
  - Sheman, Ruth
  - Sherman, Nathaniel
  - Sherman, William O'Neill
  - Sherrill, James W.
  - Sherwood-Dunn, Berkeley
  - Shestack, Audrey H.
  - Shibley, Gerald D.
  - Shields, John K.
  - Shiga, Kiyoshi
  - Shilling, E. R.
  - Shimberg, Mandell
  - Shimer, Alma E.
  - Shine, William J.
  - Shiner, William
  - Shinners, W. L.
  - Shipley, Alfred E
  - Shipley, P. G.
  - Shipman, Louis Evan
  - Shippee, Wilson
  - Shippen, L. P.
  - Shisler, John W.
  - Shoemaker, Harlan
  - Shoop, Mrs. Frederick J.
  - Shope, Richard E.
  - Shope
    Includes: Extracts from Shope's Harvey lecture
  - Shoro, Clifford C.
  - Short, William H.
  - Shotwell, James T.
  - Shovska, Ali
  - Shrady, Arthur Melville
  - Shrigley, Mrs. E. A.
  - Shriver, Alfred Jenkins
  - Shryock, Richard Harrison
  - Shull, George H.
  - Shumway, Edward A.
  - Shumway, Vivian
  - Shunk, I. V.
  - Shuster, George N.
  - Shusterman, J.
  - Sia, Richard H. P.
  - Sibley, Mrs. Charlton E.
  - Sibley, Joseph C.
  - Sicard, C.
  - Sicher, Dudley D.
  - Sicher, William D.
  - Sidbury, J. B.
  - Sidenberg, William R.
  - Sidney C. Ormsby Co.
  - Siefert, C.
  - Sieg, L. P.
  - Siegmund, Harry B.
  - Sievers, A. B.
  - Sigale, M.
  - Sigerist, Henry E.
  - Siggelkron, Wilhelm
  - Sigma XI
  - Sihler, Captain
  - Sikelianos, Eva
  - Silber, L.
  - Silberman and Hoskins
  - Siler, Joseph F.
  - Silliman, George S.
  - Silliman, H. I.
  - Sillman, Maxwell
  - Silvalruz, C.
  - Silverman, A. Clement
  - Silverman, Charles
  - Silvernail, Stephan
  - Simchowicz, T.
  - Simeto, Mario C.
  - Simkowitch, Professor
  - Simmons, George H., 1910-1934; 4 folders
    Includes: Administrative correspondence of Journal of the American Medical Association.
  - Simms, Henry Swain, 4 folders
  - Simms, Samuel
  - Simon, Charles E.
  - Simon, Frank A.
  - Simon, J.
  - Simon, Julius
  - Simon, Kurt M.
  - Simon, Sidney K.
  - Simon, Webster G.
  - Simonds, J. P.
  - Simons, John
  - Simonton, L. J.
  - Simpson, Burton T.
  - Simpson, F. F.
  - Simpson, Friench
  - Simpson, James Dundas
  - Simpson, John N.
  - Sinclair, Donald B.
  - Sinclair, Robert Rees
  - Sinclair, Upton
  - Singer, Charles
  - Singer, H. Douglas
  - Singer, Isidor
  - Singer, Paul
  - Sinn, Esther M.
  - Sinnott, Edmund W.
  - Sipprell, Clara E.
  - Sippy, John J.
  - Sire, Lillian R.
  - Sires, Edward B.
  - Sisson, Warren R.
  - Sister Xavier Maria
  - Sjemashko, N. A.
  - Sjollema, B.
  - Skerrett, Robert G.
  - Skiles, Jonah W. D.
  - Skillern, P. G.
  - Skinker, Caroline F.
  - Skinner, Joseph Osmun
  - Skinner, Mrs. Otis
  - Skinner, W. D.
  - Sklar, M.
  - Skoog, A. L.
  - Slack, Henry R.
  - Slade, Caroline M.
  - Sladen, Frank Joseph
  - Slanetz, Charles A.
  - Slater, J. C.
  - Slater, Mrs. John David
  - Slater, Mrs. Horatio N.
  - Slatter, P. A.
  - Slaughter, William H.
  - Slee, Lt.
  - Slee, Florence
  - Slee, Richard
  - Slemons, Josiah Morris
  - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr.
  - Sloane, George
  - Sloane, J. Byron
  - Slocum, Dr.
  - Slocum, H. A.
  - Slocum, M. A.
  - Slowtzoff, B.
  - Slutskin, David
  - Slye, Maud
  - Small, James C.
  - Smalley, Frances E
  - Smalley, L. A.
  - Smart, W. A.
  - Smelker, V. A.
  - Smelser, L. B.
  - Smillie, Ernest W.
  - Smillie, Wilson George, 1916-1937; 3 folders
    Includes: Correspondence on his work on cultivation of poliomyelitis at RIMR, 1916-17. Correspondence on his work for International Health Board on treatment of hookworm disease in Brazil, 1920-1921, and on dengue fever and respiratory diseases in Southern States of U.S., 1923-1928. Letter from David Edsall (copy) offering Smillie professorship of Public Health Administration and Epidemiology at Harvard University, 6/21/27. General correspondence.
  - Smith, Miss A.
  - Smith, A. E.
  - Smith, Alan DeForest
  - Smith, Alan Welch
  - Smith, Alexander
  - Smith, Alfred E.
  - Smith, Alice
  - Smith, Allen K.
  - Smith, Arthur H.
  - Smith, Arthur J.
  - Smith, Arthur L.
  - Smith, Austin E.
  - Smith, Barry C.
  - Smith, Bolton
  - Smith, C. Ernest
  - Smith, C. W.
  - Smith, Carl H.
  - Smith, Carroll
  - Smith, Carroll Dunham
  - Smith, Clarence B.
  - Smith, Corinna Lindon
  - Smith, Craig R.
  - Smith, David Eugene
  - Smith, David T.
  - Smith, Dorethea Egleston
  - Smith, E. D.
  - Smith, E. E.
  - Smith, E. Franklin
  - Smith, Edgar Fahs
  - Smith, Edith A.
  - Smith, Edric Brooks, 1915-1945; 10 folders
    Includes: Administrative correspondence on budgets, building alterations, salaries, supplies, equipment, employees, etc.
  - Smith, Elinor Van Dorn
  - Smith, Emma P.
  - Smith, Erwin F.
  - Smith, Esmonde B.
  - Smith, Eugene B.
  - Smith, Florence L.
  - Smith, Frank J., Jr.
  - Smith, Frank R.
  - Smith, Fred M.
  - Smith, G. A.
  - Smith, G. E.
  - Smith, George H.
  - Smith, George V.
  - Smith, Geraldine
  - Smith, Gertrude R.
  - Smith, Harrison
  - Smith, Harry Worcster
  - Smith, Helen Barrett
  - Smith, Herman
  - Smith, Homer W.
  - Smith, Howard R.
  - Smith, Mrs. J. E.
  - Smith, J. Gardner
  - Smith, J. Henderson
  - Smith, James Barclay
  - Smith, James D.
  - Smith, James Lorrain
  - Smith, John A.
  - Smith, John C.
  - Smith, John F.
  - Smith, John M.
  - Smith, Joseph
  - Smith, Joseph W.
  - Smith, Mrs. L. E.
  - Smith, Lawrence W.
  - Smith, Lee H.
  - Smith, Logan Pearsall
  - Smith, M. A. B.
  - Smith, Mary Agnes
  - Smith, Mildred K.
  - Smith, Milton F.
  - Smith, Nathan R.
  - Smith, Norman E.
  - Smith, O. J.
  - Smith, Philip Edward
  - Smith, R. Emerson
  - Smith, Richard R.
  - Smith, Mrs. Robert F.
  - Smith, Robert S.
  - Smith, Shirley W.
  - Smith, Theobald, 14 folders
    Includes: Correspondence on methods of production of antimeningitis and pneumococcus sera, 1913. Correspondence on purchase of land in Princeton, N.J., for RIMR Institute of Animal Pathology, 1914-15. Correspondence on research on hog cholera conducted at Princeton, 1916. Report on proposed cooperation between Institute of Animal Pathology and Walker-Gordon Laboratories Co. in prosecution of research into bovine pathology and dairy sanitation, 1918. Letter to SF on work of Dr. John W. Gowen and possibility of asking him to work at Princeton, which would mean introducing genetics and statistical methods research to Institute, 5/20/21. Letter from SF on RIMR's offer to Karl Meyer of a post at Princeton Institute, 6/21/21. Correspondence concerning Dr. Howe at Princeton Institute, SF expressing opinion that Howe should be retained longer, 1924. Correspondence on bringing Dr. Paul A. Lewis to Princeton, and on possibility of asking Sewall Wright to Princeton in the event of having to replace Dr. Gowen, 1924. Correspondence about Lewis's work, 1928. General administrative correspondence concerning Institute of Animal Pathology. Some biographical materials.
    - Folder 1, 1913-1914
    - Folder 2, 1915-1916
    - Folder 3, 1917
    - Folder 4, 1918
    - Folder 5, 1919
    - Folder 6, 1920
    - Folder 7, 1921-1922
    - Folder 8, 1923-1924; 1931-1932
    - Folder 9, 1925-1927
    - Folder 10, 1928
    - Folder 11, 1929-1930
    - Folder 12, 1931-1932
    - Folder 13, 1933-1935
    - Minute on Doctor Theobald Simth, 1935
  - Smith, W. A.
  - Smith, W. Richmond
  - Smith, William Adams
  - Smith, William R.
  - Smith, William Sidney
  - Smith, Mrs. Wilson
  - Smith, Winford H.
  - Smith College
  - Smithburn, Kenneth C.
  - Smithe, D. O.
  - Smithe, F. L.
  - Smithies, Frank
  - Smithsonian Institution
  - Smyly, H. Jocelyn
  - Smyth, Francis Scott
  - Smyth, Nathan A.
  - Smythe, C. V.
  - Smythe, Clara
  - Smythe, J. D.
  - Snapper, I.
  - Sneed, William L.
  - Snell, Cornelia T.
  - Snell, John A.
  - Snively, A. Barr
  - Snow, Congdon G.
  - Snow, Elliott
  - Snow, Frank Whipple
  - Snow, H. W.
  - Snow, Irving M.
  - Snow, William Benham
  - Snow, William F.
  - Snowden, R. R.
  - Snyder, A.
  - Snyder, O. B.
  - Snyder, R. G.
  - Snyder, William
  - Soboleski, Michael
  - Sobotka, Harry H.
  - Social Register Association
  - Socialist Suffrage Committee
  - Sociedad Argentina de Patalogia
  - Sociedad Medica Veracruzana
  - Society for Cinematographic Instruction in medicine and surgery
  - Society for experimental biology and medicine
  - Society for visual education
  - Society of the Friends of Music
  - Sorensen, Einar
  - Sorensen, S. P. S.
  - Soifer, Albert A.
  - Sokoloff, Boris
  - Soldateuskov, Basil
  - Soler, Blanco
  - Solis-Cohen, Myer
  - Solis-Cohen, Solomon
  - Sollmann, Torald
  - Solomon, Harry C.
  - Solomon, Mrs. Harry C.
  - Solomon, Leo
  - Solovieff, M. N.
  - Soltz, Thomas
  - Somerville, E.
  - Sommer, Henry Otto
  - Sonberg, Albert
  - Sondern, Frederic Ewald, 2 folders
  - Sonnenfeld, Julius
  - Sooy, Joseph W.
  - Soper, Alexander C., Jr.
  - Soper, George A.
  - Sophian, Abraham
  - Sorapine, O.
  - Soresi, Angelo L.
  - Sorgievsky, Nicholas N.
  - Sosman, Merrill C.
  - Soule, Karl Thayer
  - Soulet, Mrs. L.
  - Soulet, Malcolm H.
  - Source Research Council Inc.
  - South, L. H.
  - South African Institute for Medical Research
  - Southard, Elmer E.
  - Southard, J. G.
  - Southard, Mary Young
  - Souther, R. G.
  - Southern Medical Association
  - Souttar, Henry S.
  - Soutter, R.
  - Souza, G. H. De Paula
  - Souza Novelog Narcisco
  - Soza, Ezequiel
  - Spaeth, Edmund B.
  - Spafford, Edward E.
  - Spalding, H. N.
  - Spano, Rocco Antonio
  - Sparks, J. W.
  - Sparks, John B.
  - Sparrow, Louise Kidder
  - Spartalis, George M.
  - Spatz, B.
  - Spaulding, Mrs.
  - Spaulding, Edith R.
  - Spaulding, H. M.
  - Spear, Olive
  - Speare, M. Edmund
  - Speciale
  - Spector, I. I.
  - Speel, Mrs. Byron
  - Speer, Harry
  - Speer, Marvin E., Jr.
  - Spelman, John D.
  - Spelman, Laura M.
  - Spemann, Hans
  - Spencer, Mrs. E. A.
  - Spencer, Robert D.
  - Spencer Lens Company
  - Sperber, Perry
  - Sperry, Joel A.
  - Speyer, H.
  - Sphere (London newspaper)
  - Spiegel, A.
  - Spiegelberg, Flora
  - Spielmeyer, W.
  - Spies, Charles B., 1916-1938; 3 folders
  - Spies, Marjory Webb
  - Spiller, William G.
  - Spindler, E.
  - Spingarn, Arthur B.
  - Spiro, Karl
  - Spittler, F. A.
  - Spoerl, Elsie
  - Spolverini, Luigi M.
  - Spooner, Florence L.
  - Spoor, John A.
  - Sporborg, Constance A.
  - Sprague, Frances R.
  - Sprague, Frank
  - Sprague, George P.
  - Sprague, Rufus W., Jr.
  - Spranklin, John William
  - Spriesterbach, David O.
  - Spring Rice, Margery L.
  - Springarm, Arthur B.
  - Springer, Constance L.
  - Springer, Julius
  - Spronk, C. H. H.
  - Sproul, Robert G.
  - Sproul, William C.
  - Sprunt, T(?). P.
  - Spurling, R. Glen
  - Squibb, H. A.
  - Squier, George Owen
  - Srivastavu, B. P.
  - Staadeker, Jerome B.
  - Staatl. Bakteriologische
  - Staats, Zeitung
  - Stachlin, Edward
  - Stack, John
  - Stack, Sir Lee
  - Stadie, William Christopher
  - Staehelin, Rudolf
  - Stafford, C. M.
  - Stafford, H. G.
  - Stafford, Jane
  - Stafford Hendrix Co.
  - Stahl, Alice
  - Stahl, Arthur W.
  - Stahl, Mildred Farmer
  - Stahl, William M.
  - Stalker, Hugh
  - Stamp, Louis
  - Stampo, Mrs. H B.
  - Standle, T. H.
  - Stanford University
  - Stanistreet, G. B.
  - Stanley, Arthur
  - Stanley, Camp
  - Stanley, Wendell Meredith, 1935-1941; 18 items
    Includes: General correspondence. Letters to SF on his isolation of three types of tobacco mosaic virus, using chemical methods to isolate three different crystalline proteins, and also on his work on inactivation of tobacco mosaic virus through chemical action on the amino groups of the active protein of virus, 4/7, 6/8/36.
  - Stanley-Brown, Margaret
  - Stanton, E. Mac D.
  - Stanton, Edward L.
  - Stanton, F. L.
  - Stanton, J. M.
  - Stanton, S. C.
  - Stapleton, Thomas C.
  - Starin, William Alfred
  - Stark, Dr.
  - Stark, H. H.
  - Starkey, T. A.
  - Starley, W. F.
  - Starling, Ernest H.
  - Starr, Harris E.
  - Starr, M. Allen
  - Starr, Sarah Logan Wister
  - Starrett, Elsie A.
  - Stasney, Joseph
  - State Charities Aid Association, 1910-1935; 6 folders
    Includes: General and administrative correspondencea about meetings, amendments to by-laws, reports, etc.
  - Staub, Albert W.
  - Staude, Ernest M.
  - Stauffer, Nathan P.
  - Stazione Bacologia Sperimentale
  - Steahert, G. E. and Co.
  - Stearns, Maude E.
  - Stearns, Walter W.
  - Stebbins, Ernest L.
  - Stebbins, Frances F.
  - Stebbins, George L.
  - Stedman, Thomas L.
  - Steele, B. P.
  - Steele, F. A.
  - Steele, H. Merriman
  - Steele, Murray
  - Steen, Carl
  - Steensland, H. S.
  - Steese, Edwin S.
  - Steeves, Mrs. G. Walter
  - Stefano, James
  - Stegman, Henry M.
  - Stein, Arthur
  - Stein, Cora N.